vssecretrewards.com 2015-06-30

# Victoria's Secret Privacy & Security

This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected through this Web site, how that information is used, to whom it's disclosed, and how it's safeguarded. Unless indicated otherwise, this policy applies only to personal information collected through the Web site, microsites, or mobile sites of our brands and lines of business that expressly adopt, and display or link to, this policy. These brands and lines of business include Victoria's Secret, Victoria's Secret Pink, and Pink Nation. By "personal information" we mean your identifying information (like name, home address, and email address), and descriptive information (like tastes and preferences) if coupled with your identifying information. We may refer to Victoria's Secret, Victoria's Secret Pink (or "Pink"), and Pink Nation (by Pink) as "we," "us," or "our" throughout this privacy policy.

###  This privacy policy answers these questions:

  * What personal information is collected and how is it used?
  * How is technology used to serve our advertisements on other Web sites and what choices do you have?
  * How does this Web site interact with third-party Web sites and content?
  * What information do we share with third parties and our sister brands (or what information may they access because of the services they provide to us)?
  * What choices do you have over how your information is used?
  * How do you update your personal information?
  * How do we address children's privacy?
  * How do we secure your information on our site?
  * Where is personal information stored and processed?
  * Whom should you contact with questions or concerns?
  * When was this policy last updated?

###  What personal information is collected and how is it used?

  1. ####  1\.  Information You Directly Provide through our Site

We collect personal information directly from you to do all the things typically associated with Web sites. Examples of the information we collect include name, address, phone number, email address, personal preferences, credit card number, purchase and ordering information, demographical information, responses to survey questions and sizing information.

This information is collected at various places on our site: for instance, when you check out with your online order; subscribe to catalogs, email offers, and Pink mobile messaging offers; participate in surveys; join Victoria's Secret Pink Nation; enter contests or sweepstakes; or interact with special-event or program offers.

We may also collect information that you provide on our site about people you know. For example, we collect your gift recipient's contact information to process your gift orders. We may also collect contact information about your friends and family members when you participate in one of our refer-a-friend programs. In these instances, we may send a message to your friend or family member on your behalf. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the message from you.

We use personal information to do things like:

    * process your online orders;
    * open an online account at your request;
    * personalize your online experience with content and offers that are tailored to your interests;
    * provide customer service, whether it's responding to a request or following up on an order;
    * include you in surveys and contests;
    * enable you to post your content, such as comments or images;
    * facilitate networks of online social activity centered around our products and services;
    * improve our website, improve the manner in which offers are made on our website, improve purchase decisions of our visitors and the interactions visitors have with our website;
    * enable you to interact with third-party content service providers, whether by linking to their sites, viewing their content within our Web environment, or by viewing our content within their Web environment; and
    * market our products and services that may be of interest to you--for instance, we may add you to the Victoria's Secret and Victoria's Secret Pink email list when you make an online purchase or sign up to receive emails; or we may add you to Victoria's Secret print-catalogue list when you make an online purchase or to the Pink Nation email list if you sign up for Pink Nation.
  2. ####  2\.  Information We Observe or Collect through Technology

    1. #####  a.  Navigational Information

When you visit this Web site, we collect navigational information, such as browser type and version, service-provider identification, IP address, the site from which you came, and the site to which you navigate. Navigational information is largely anonymous in the sense that it doesn't contain your name, address, phone number, email address or other information that directly identifies you. However, we may associate this navigational information with your personal information if you provide it.

    2. #####  b.  Cookies and Clear gifs

To better understand what you do while on this Web site, we use a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that's stored by your Web browser on your computer. It's used to do things like see how you navigate this Web site, what you click on, and remember you and your online purchases when you return. This helps us improve our site, provide better customer service, tailor your online experience, and tailor offers to you based on your unique tastes and both your online and offline (e.g., in-store) interactions and purchase history.

We also use clear-gifs (also known as a Web beacon or Web bug) on this Web site and in our emails. A clear gif is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or e-mail message. It helps us do things like view the URL of the page on which the clear gif appears and the time this Web site or email in question is viewed. Clear gifs in e-mails help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails, including those that you forward to friends and family; and they help deliver a more personalized online experience. These technologies may be used to help us see which of our interactive experiences online users like most�for example, by keeping track of the number of times a video, widget or other media is accessed or embedded on social networking sites; and on which social networking sites it is embedded, based on inquiries that are sent to this Web site. Cookies and clear gifs also allow us to associate your online navigational information, or purchases and interactions (both online and offline), with any personal information you provide (such as name, address, phone number, survey responses, and email address). We'll associate this information to deliver products and services to you; to improve our business; to transact business; and to market our products and services on this and other Web sites and through a variety of media like email, mobile advertising, and direct mail. As an example, we may use cookies to keep track of what you put into your shopping bag. That can help us contact you if your online session is disrupted in mid-purchase, resulting in an abandoned cart. We can also use this technology to determine whether you'd be interested in participating in special events, given your preferences. The end result is a more personalized experience that's tailored to your needs and tastes.

For information about your options with respect to cookies, see "What choices do you have over how your information is used?" below.

  3. ####  3\.  Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology

We evaluate and select third-party service providers to help us provide certain features on this site and analyze our visitors' site and purchase preferences. The following provides more information about these service providers.

    1. #####  a.  Features

We use third-party services to provide certain features on this Web site. These third parties use some or all of the technologies described in Information We Observe or Collect Through Technology to provide these features.

    2. #####  b.  Analysis

We use analytics companies to better understand your use of this Web site, and Web capabilities like embeddable widgets. For instance, these third parties may serve surveys to determine satisfaction with the Web site and then tie the responses to actual behavior on the Web site. We also use third parties so that we can evaluate and understand your online and store purchases to provide tailored offers and information to you. This information also allows us to improve this Web site, and Web capabilities. They accomplish this by using some or all of the technologies described in Information We Observe or Collect Through Technology.

Back To Top

###  How is technology used to serve our advertisements on other Web sites and what choices do you have?

We contract with third-party advertising companies, such as Google Analytics, to deliver tailored online display and banner advertising to you on other Web sites. To serve this advertising, these third-party companies place, use, or rely on technology, such as cookies and clear gifs, to obtain information about customer interactions with us through our Web sites and interactions with other Web sites. Once this information is gathered, it helps us select tailored ads for placement on these other Web sites, based on a customer�s combined online and offline (e.g., in-store) shopping history and experience with us.

For information about opt out programs that these third party advertising companies participate in, and the effect of opting out, click the following: [[NAI Opt Out]](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), [[DAA Opt Out]](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), and [[Google Analytics]](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) (you'll then leave this site for online sites where you may specify your preferences under those programs). You can also click the preference icon that may appear on some of our advertising served through use of these technologies. You should also note that our systems do not recognize Do Not Track headers from Web browsers.

Back To Top

###  How does this Web site interact with third-party Web sites and content?

We may enable you to navigate to third-party sites and services, or otherwise display third-party content. We do this for your convenience. We don't endorse or generally have any affiliation with these third parties. And we don't control and aren't responsible for their Web practices. It is possible that the third party providing content through our Web site may collect or observe information through its use of technology. Whether the third-party content appears within our Web environment (like a map frame), or you leave our Web site for another site to view it, those service provider's terms, conditions, and privacy policies govern your online experience (unless we post a statement that indicates otherwise). Please view their terms of service and privacy policies if you have any question about their practices.

Here's a partial list of the sites or content of these third parties:

  1. #####  1\.  Interactive Maps

We may facilitate easy access to the online maps of content providers like Google, Microsoft, and Yahoo! There you can get quick location, driving, and contact information for our stores.

  2. #####  2\.  Inline Framing

We may provide content on our Web site that exists on other Web sites, such as live or recorded video, through a frame surrounded by content from our Web site (this framed content is referred to as an iFrame). The iFrame is used to facilitate easy access to the content from the other Web site.

  3. #####  3\.  Sweepstakes, Contests, and Survey Sites

We may rely on the expertise of third-party service providers to run sweepstakes, contests, and surveys. Navigation to these sites may be seamless so that it appears you're still in our Web site environment. In these cases, the third-party's privacy policy may apply to any personal information you provide in connection with the event. So please take note of who's running the event in question; and the terms, conditions, and policies that apply.

  4. #####  4\.  Social Networking or Other User-Generated-Content Sites, and Other Websites

We may at times facilitate easy access to third-party sites, like social networking sites and other sites that host user-generated content. This may include easy click-through access or even "single sign-on" to these sites. The third-party's privacy policy applies to any personal information you provide at these sites.

  5. #####  5\.  The Angel Credit Card Site

We enable you to navigate easily to the site of Comenity Bank (Comenity), where you can apply for the Angel card and pay invoices online. Comenity issues and owns the Angel credit card accounts. When you apply online for an Angel credit card or pay your account online, you leave our site and interact directly with Comenity. Any information you provide to Comenity is subject to Comenity's terms, conditions, and policies, including its privacy policy.

  6. #####  6\.  Third-Party Rewards or Membership Programs

We may interact with certain unrelated companies that offer their customers memberships to participate in programs, which may include rewards for purchases from us. If you become a member of one of these programs or purchase something from us at this Web site through such a program, we may provide the company administering the membership program enough information about you or your purchase (like contact information, transaction date, transaction amount, and order number), to enable it to honor your membership. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the companies sponsoring these membership programs. Their terms, conditions, and policies apply to any information that's provided to them to further their programs.

  7. #####  7\.  International Checkout

We work with eShopWorld to sell and deliver our products to certain international destinations. If you are shipping to a country supported by eShopWorld, you will navigate away from our Web site to a co-branded checkout site "powered by eShopWorld." eShopWorld's privacy policy, and not our privacy policy, will apply to information that you directly provide on that site, such as your payment information. However, we and other parties will continue to use certain technologies, as described in Sections 2 (Information We Observe or Collect through Technology) and 3 (Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology) of this policy, to collect information about your online activities on that site. Additionally, when you navigate to eShopWorld's checkout site, we will share information about you and your order with eShopWorld to facilitate your purchase of our products from eShopWorld. Please see eShopWorld's privacy policy for information about its privacy practices.

Back To Top

We may share information about you with third parties, as described below, and as otherwise described in this policy:

  1. #####  1\.  Our Sister Brands

We may also share the information described in this policy, like postal and email address, customer preferences, and purchase history within our corporate family so that our affiliates may market to you. Our affiliates include such brands as Bath & Body Works, Henri Bendel, White Barn Candle Co., and La Senza International.

  2. #####  2\.  Contractors

We use third-party "back-office" contractors to help handle parts of our business because of their expertise, resources, or scale. They help us do things like fulfill orders, process payments, provide some customer service through chat features, monitor site activity, serve surveys and provide analysis from the surveys when combined with website use, maintain databases, administer and monitor emails,(e.g., from Victoria's Secret or Pink Nation), administer and send mobile messages (e.g., from Pink), serve ads on this and other Web sites as described above and provide consulting services. Contractors may also assist us in hosting microsites and mobile Web sites where you may provide personal information about you and others you know; and where they may observe information about you in the same way as described above (see What Personal Information Is Collected At Our Web Site, and How Is It Used?).

  3. #####  3\.  Other Marketers

We may share your name, postal address, and summary purchase information with other merchants and merchant exchanges. Other merchants may, in turn, use this information to send you offers on their products and services. If you don't want this information shared with these merchants and exchanges, please **click here**.

  4. #####  4\.  Law Enforcement and Emergency Response

We may disclose specific information about our Web-site visitors if we have a good-faith belief that it's necessary or authorized under the law to protect our customers, the public, or our business.

  5. #####  5\.  Sale or Merger

In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets, including a brand or line of business, consumer information may be one of the business assets that are transferred in connection with the transaction.

Nothing in this policy restricts our ability to share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you.

Back To Top

###  What choices do you have over how your information is used?

  1. #####  1\.  Email

You may remove yourself from the Victoria's Secret and Victoria's Secret Pink email list by following the removal instructions located at the bottom of each commercial email or by completing the [removal from e-mail form](https://ebm.cheetahmail.com/r/regf2?a=0&aid=477251442&email=&fp_redirected=1). If you have joined Pink Nation, you may receive Pink Nation email. If at any time you'd like to stop future delivery of Pink Nation email offers, simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each Pink Nation message. Opting out of any of these emails will not stop operational or transactional messages such as password-reset or account related information from the brand or line of business in question. We may occasionally provide you with the opportunity to opt in to receive email messages from third parties. If you do opt in, we'll share your e-mail address with the specific third party in question. Please review their privacy policies to see how they treat your personal information.

  2. #####  2\.  Mobile Messaging

If you've signed up for mobile text messaging offers (e.g., from Pink) but later decide you no longer wish to receive these offers, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message.

  3. #####  3\.  Postal Mail: Catalogs

If you'd like to specify your preferences for our catalogues (including our postal-mail offers), simply follow the instructions on each such catalogue, or dial 1-800-411-5116. To reduce postal mail **click here**.

  4. #####  4\.  Victoria's Secret Pink Nation

Please keep in mind that Pink Nation is a separate and stand-alone program, which you may join by visiting the Pink Nation Web site. Accordingly, your unsubscribe preferences for Victoria's Secret and Victoria's Secret Pink won't affect your Pink Nation preferences (and vice versa). Please specify those preferences separately.

  5. #####  5\.  Cookies and Clear Gifs

You may always choose to block cookies or even clear cookies from your computer. Simply follow your browser's instructions on how to block and clear cookies. Note that blocking cookies may not block the "first-party" cookies that are placed on your computer when you visit this site. By first-party cookies, we mean those cookies (whether placed by us or a contractor) that help us see how visitors use this site, and enable us to deliver our ads on our Web sites and other Web sites. Otherwise, clearing cookies after each visit here will prevent observations from multiple sessions being aggregated over time. Please consider the consequences of blocking or clearing cookies. Many Web sites rely on their cookies to provide you with services or features that you have requested or expect. With respect to cookies used as part of a survey, if you do not want the use of cookies to associate survey responses with your behavior on the site, you can elect to not take the survey.

  6. #####  6\.  Other Marketers

If you don't want your basic contact and purchase information shared with other marketers (other than our affiliates and our contractor/service providers), please click here.

  7. #####  7\.  Our Affiliates

If you don't want your contact and purchase information shared between our affiliates (such as Bath & Body Works), please call 1-800-411-5116 and request not to have your information shared.

Back To Top

###  How do you update your personal information?

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. You may update or modify your billing- and shipping-related information, and other account information, by logging onto our sites (e.g., Your Account on the Victoria's Secret and Victoria's Secret Pink Web site, or Edit Profile on your Pink Nation account). You may also update or modify your catalog mailing information by clicking here.

Back To Top

###  How do we address children's privacy?

We do not knowingly collect information provided by children under the age of 13.

Back To Top

###  How do we secure your information on our site?

Our Web site has the following types of security measures: limited access data-centers, firewall technology, and (for our e-Commerce sites through which you may place orders) secure-socket-layer (SSL) certificate authentication. SSL is encryption technology that provides security for information that's transmitted over the Internet.

While we implement the above security measures on our site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

Back To Top

###  Where is personal information stored and processed?

Victoria's Secret parent company L Brands, Inc. is a global organization, with affiliated legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. As the majority of our administrative and technical support functions are headquartered in the US we share, store and process personal information in the United States of America. Customers accessing and purchasing with our sales website will be interacting with servers and services provided from within the United States of America.

We may share or store your personal information among L Brands, Inc. brands and affiliates globally and transfer it to our business partners based in various countries in the world where we do business.

When we transfer your personal information internationally we will take steps to ensure that your personal information is treated lawfully in the manner we describe in this privacy policy.

If you wish to make an EU-related inquiry about privacy or data transfer, please contact our [Vice President (VP) of Legal & Compliance Services](https://www.victoriassecret.com/)

Back To Top

###  Whom should you contact with questions or concerns?

  1. #####  1\.  General inquiries

If you have general questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.

  2. #####  2\.  Specific Questions about this Policy

For specific questions, concerns, or complaints contact our Vice President (VP) of Legal and Compliance Services, who administers this policy. You may contact this person by letter or email at:

VP, Privacy   
Legal & Compliance Services   
L Brands, Inc.   
3 Limited Parkway   
Columbus, OH 43230   
US   
[generalcounsel@lb.com ](mailto:generalcounsel@limitedbrands.com)(ATTN: Privacy Matter)

Back To Top

###  When was this policy last updated?

Please click here to view any material and substantive changes made since the last revision of this privacy policy. If you're concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about VictoriasSecret.com.

This Privacy Statement is effective December 19, 2014.

Back To Top
  *[IP]: Internet Protocol
  *[SSL]: Secure Sockets Layer
